Guide to the David Sullivan U.S. Maoism Collection TAM 527
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X: Artifacts and Other Ephemera, 1965-1993
  - Postcards: China (art), undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Postcards: China: Beijing, undated (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Postcards: China: Changchun, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Postcards: China: Mao Tsetung, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Postcards: China: Memorial of the First National Congress of the Communist Party of China, undated (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Postcards: China: Peking Hotel, undated (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Postcards: China (people), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Postcards: China (people), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Postcards: China (people), circa 1993 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Postcards: China (people), undated (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Postcards: China (places), 1972 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Postcards: China (places), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Postcards: China (places), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Postcards: China (places), undated (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Postcards: China: "Red Detachment of Women" (ballet), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Postcards: China: Tibet, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Postcards: China: The West Lake, undated (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Scrolls: China/ Chinese Communist Party (4 items), 1978, undated (Box 21)
  - Scrolls: China/ Chinese Communist Party (6 items), undated (Box 22)
  - Stencils (2 items), undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Travel Guides and Maps: China, undated (Box 19, Folder 63)